## **Martin Elizbaryan**

**CONTACT INFORMATION** Address: The 4th Vracakan lane 7 building 51 ap , Yerevan

**Phone:** +374 93 143 600 **Date of birth:** Apr 29, 1995

**Nationality:** Armenian



**OBJECTIVE** 

Hi, my name is Martin Elizbaryan and I'm a full stack developer and tutor in TCO Team. I have had more than

500 students who are now working as a web developers.

I have about 3+ years' experience building websites for clients all over the world

**EXPERIENCE** 

Feb 2020 - Present Laravel Developer

TCO Team

Jan 2020 - Sep 2020 Laravel Developer

M&D Systems

Jan 2019 - Dec 2019 Laravel Developer

IFC Markets

Sep 2018 - Jan 2019 **Tutor** 

**Profit Development Company** 

**EDUCATION** 

2012 - 2018 Bachelor of Cybernetics

National Polytechnic University Of Armenia

**LANGUAGES** 

**SKILLS** 

Armenian Html Css

Russian Bootstrap Material UI

Russian jQuery

English

VueJS ReactJS

Php MySql

Laravel Node JS

Prisma Git

PROJECTS https://www.ifcmarkets.com/

https://private.ifcmarkets.com/en/login

https://sertx.eu/login